ng on Adam's augmentations, a gun may not even be remotely necessary to escape unha
oming and didn't have a spare gun you picked up on the way, giving him one of your 
n contrast, the sawed-off shotgun's extremely high damage output is hampered by its
 liability than help. The GEP gun is about the only one that's any useful. The plas
ling an enemy. The combat shotgun, when loaded with buckshot, is pretty useful for 
lking past. Given that pepper gun ammo can be found throughout the game, and how la
isc-One Nuke: Picking the GEP gun when offered to you by Paul is probably the best 
 sniper rifle, a sawn-off shotgun and an assault rifle, not to mention a handful of
or UNATCO troops will run and gun, although the running often consists of running a
 repeatedly requested a 'skul-gun' inserted into his head, so he can shoot people b
at the shock of firing such a gun would fry what brain he did have pretty quickly. 
elf, and ammo for the heftier guns is limited. You pretty much have to sneak around
ilbert Renton also asks for a gun to take out the gangster Jojo Fine by himself and
rticularly ludicrous with shotguns: max out the rifle skills, and all the pellets f
rom shotgun blasts will hit exactly in the centre of the cros
g you one-hit-kill sniper shotguns. Improvised Weapon: The crowbar, any heavy objec
t becomes possible to run and gun successfully: with the proper augmentations JC is
y with pistols, sawed-off shotguns, or mini-crossbows (granted, in this game pistol
Armor equipped with twin chainguns that do much more damage than any other automati
e equipped with full-auto shotguns or dragon tooth swords, and explode when they di
role, equipped with a machine gun and being heavily armored against ballistic ordin
lethal force, he will happily gun down every NSF troop who gets in his way. Which b
ome to Use: For some, the GEP gun. The basic pistol or stealth pistol can fall into
bartender has a sawed-off shotgun behind the counter. However, she also carries her
y Park, then chase after him, guns a-blazing. Or better yet, give him a candy bar f
You can give Gilbert Renton a gun, let him kill Jojo, watch as his daughter Sandra 
